myownbusiness.org 2015-06-14

# My Own Business Inc - Privacy Policy

|  [home](http://www.myownbusiness.org/) | [about us](http://www.myownbusiness.org/mission_purpose.html) | privacy policy  |   
   
|  **Privacy Policy**

We are committed to protecting your privacy. 

**Registration:**  
Registration is necessary in order to take access course content. Information is collected to ensure that **My Own Business, Inc.** is developing products and services to meet the needs of people starting businesses. 

**My Own Business, Inc.** will never sell, rent or provide any personal information to any third party, unless required to do so by law. All information is secured in a safe data environment. 

**Personal Business Plans:**  
A blank template for your business plan can be downloaded to your computer. You may utilize this to prepare your personal business plan in complete privacy. 

**Feedback Comments and Suggestions:**  
Feedback is voluntary and will be used solely to improve the course and/or to provide statistical data which can be used to obtain funding from non-profit sources. By using our web site and submitting your feedback, you consent to the collection and use of this information by My Own Business, Inc. 

**Information Sharing:**  
No personal information is furnished to any third parties. 

**Changes:**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it. 

|  |  |
